unlockedprofiles.com 2009-12-26

# PowerNetX, Inc - Privacy Policy

We have created this Privacy Policy in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. This Privacy Policy explains our practices with respect to the collection, use, and disclosure of personal and non-personal information provided by visitors to our Web site. By using this site, you signify your assent to these our privacy practices and the terms and conditions of our Web site. 

If this policy is not agreeable to you, please do not use this site.

**WHAT TYPE INFORMATION IS COLLECTED?**

**_Personal Information_**  
We only collect personal information from visitors to our Web site when they voluntarily provide it to us by completing our registration form or electing to use one of our services. We may require visitors to provide us with information including, but not limited to, their name, physical address, email address, birth date, username and password. 

**_Non-Personal Information_**  
When visitors access our Web site, certain non-personal information may be collected from them including, but not limited to, their browser type (e.g., Netscape or Internet Explorer), operating system (e.g., Windows or Macintosh), IP address, and the domain name from which they accessed the site (e.g., lycos.com). In addition, we may collect information about visitors' browsing behavior, such as the date and time they visit the Web site, the areas or pages of our Web site that they visit, the amount of time spent viewing the site, the number of times the visitor returns to the site, and click-stream data. We use transparent tracking pixels to determine the number of Web site visitors that have been sent to us through our affiliate network. We do not track any information about visitors once they leave our site. We may use cookies (small text files that are stored on visitors computers when they access our Web site) to collect this information. Information collected through cookies may be combined with visitors' personal information. We may also allow unaffiliated third parties, such as advertisers, to serve cookies to visitors of our Web site. Visitors are always free to decline cookies, but in doing so they may not be able to use certain features on our Web site. The "help" segment of the toolbar on most browsers explains how to configure a browser to not accept new cookies, how to have the browser inform a user when they receive a new cookie, and how to erase cookies from their hard drives. 

**USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION AND DISCLAIMER**

By the use of the Site or its services, the Member, visitor or User expressly agrees that the Site may use any information that it gathers or collects about the Member, visitor or User including personal information that has been provided by the Member, visitor or User for technical, administration, research and development, customer administration, age verification, marketing, promotional and advertising use and for the transmission of email communications, the sending of products or the fulfilling of any terms and conditions; and furthermore that the Site such personal information will be kept confidental by only in-house, for purposes of providing such goods and services. NO PERSONAL INFORATION WILL BE SHARED WITH ANY THIRD PARTIES WITHOUT CUSTOMER'S PERMISSION

By your acts of signing up as a subscriber to the Site, accepting the Terms and Conditions of the Site and affirmatively consenting to accept emails from this Site.

**“OPT-OUT” – REVOCATION OF CONSENT PROCEDURE**  
The Site also offers all Members and Users a procedure for “Opting-Out” if the Member or User subsequently chooses to revoke or withdraw any consent to receive Offers by sending an e-mail to [support@sextronix.com](mailto:support@sextronix.com) clearly stating that the Member or User has revoked or withdrawn consent to receive any future Offers.

**DISCLOSURE**  
We will not disclose or use any of your personally identifiable information except to the extent set forth in this Privacy Policy, or under special circumstances, such as when we believe in good faith that the law requires it, or when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to enforce any of our rights and terms and conditions or identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating the Terms and Conditions.

**WHAT SECURITY MEASURES DO WE TAKE TO PROTECT YOUR DATA?**  
To help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data integrity, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place certain physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect from visitors to our Web site. We use SSL (Secure Socket Layer) technology to protect any credit card information you provide us. We allow access to personal information only to persons and entities engaging in activities provided for by this Privacy Policy. Visitors should consider any communication that they transmit to us (such as data, questions or answers, comments, suggestions, or communications submitted to a chat room) to be non-confidential. We will not be liable or responsible if information that belongs to a visitor is intercepted and used by an unintended recipient. 

**WE PROTECT CHILDREN'S PRIVACY**  
Protecting the privacy of children is VERY important to us. For that reason we do not structure any part of our site to attract anyone under the age of 18 (21 in some areas) and we do not allow anyone under the age of 18 (21 in some areas) to register and become a member of our site. 

**ACCEPTANCE OF PRIVACY TERMS & CONDITIONS**  
By visiting this Web site, you are agreeing to the practices described in this Privacy Policy. By visiting this site, you also accept, without limitation or qualification, all terms and conditions concerning the use of this site. We may at any time revise these terms and conditions. You are bound by any such revisions and should therefore periodically visit this page to review the then-current terms and conditions to which you are bound. To the extent that any of the third-party sites accessible through our Web site (such as our advertisers) have different privacy practices from those stated in this Privacy Policy, those third-party privacy practices govern the collection and use of information you provide when visiting those sites. We are not responsible for the policies, content, and practices of other companies. 

**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**  
There may be times when we need to change the terms of this Privacy Policy. To ensure that you are aware of our current privacy practices, please bookmark this page and check back often. 

**HOW TO CANCEL YOUR SUBSCRIPTION**  
You can cancel your subscription anytime online by visiting our [Cancel Page](http://www.sextronix.com/cancel/).

**HOW CAN YOU ACCESS THE INFORMATION WE HAVE COLLECTED FROM YOU?**  
Visitors who wish to access or change the information they provided to our Web site, should visit the [Customer Service](http://support.sextronix.com/) of this site or contact us via [Email](mailto:support@sextronix.com). 

**HOW CAN YOU CONTACT THE WEB SITE OPERATOR?**  
Visitors who have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or their interactions with this Web site, should visit the [Customer Service](http://support.sextronix.com/) of this site or contact us via [Email](mailto:support@sextronix.com).
